<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="blogs/news/tagged/product.atom"/>
  <title>Impact Theme Sound - Blog</title>
  <updated>2022-08-05T15:16:14+02:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Impact Theme Sound</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>blogs/news/never-play-the-same-with-mg20-wireless-gaming-headphones</id>
    <published>2022-08-05T14:30:42+02:00</published>
    <updated>2022-09-13T08:50:39+02:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="blogs/news/never-play-the-same-with-mg20-wireless-gaming-headphones"/>
    <title>Never Play The Same With MG20 Wireless Gaming Headphones</title>
    <author>
      <name>Stanislas Pichutka</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Master &amp; Dynamic is thrilled to introduce the new MG20 Wireless Gaming Headphones. Breaking ground in the gaming category as the first true luxury gaming headphones</span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="blogs/news/never-play-the-same-with-mg20-wireless-gaming-headphones">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h5>Master &amp; Dynamic is thrilled to introduce the new MG20 Wireless Gaming Headphones. Breaking ground in the gaming category as the first true luxury gaming headphones.</h5>
<p>the MG20 is crafted from magnesium, lambskin leather, and Alcantara® and features a detachable boom microphone with an additional on-board mic array for clear communication in-game and on calls. 50mm Beryllium drivers and 7.1 surround sound provide brilliant acoustics so you can truly lose yourself in the game.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>We knew the time was right to create a luxury gaming headset, and our goal with the MG20 was to deliver the exceptional sound and design that Master &amp; Dynamic is known for. The MG20 will satisfy both the professional and recreational gamer looking for technical performance, sophisticated style and high quality materials.</p>
</blockquote>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Jonathan Levine, Founder and CEO of Master &amp; Dynamic</strong></p>
<figure><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0646/2118/3226/files/x3_mg20.png?v=1659703219" alt="MG20 Wireless Gaming Headphones">
<figcaption>The MG20 features an Alcantara® headband and memory foam ear pads for unrivaled comfort, Bluetooth 5.0 creates a secure connection for a 100ft/30m distance, available in Black Onyx and Galactic White</figcaption>
</figure>
<p>The MG20 Wireless Gaming Headphones offer a host of new features designed to optimize performance. Enjoy immersive sound thanks to 50mm Beryllium drivers and 7.1 surround sound. The MG20 also includes Qualcomm® aptX™ HD for music, and aptX™ Low-Latency for mobile gaming, and for the first time ever, an in-app equalizer in the M&amp;D Connect app will allow users to choose between sound profiles. The MG20’s angled ear cups align to the ear’s natural shape and semi-open back acoustics create a wider, more lifelike soundstage. An elegant, detachable boom microphone provides the ultimate in-game talk clarity while an additional on-board microphone array allows for clear communication even when not gaming.</p>
<figure><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0646/2118/3226/files/x3_mg20_2.png?v=1659704136" alt="MG20 Wireless Gaming Headphones">
<figcaption>The MG20 features up to 22 hours of playtime and uses on-head detection to save battery and detachable boom microphone provides the ultimate in-game talk clarity.</figcaption>
</figure>
<p>A bold expression of minimalist design, the MG20 has anodized aluminum and lightweight magnesium ear cups that create an unmatched strength-to-weight ratio for comfort and durability. The gaming headphone's sleek shape provides a sophisticated look whether gaming, working, or on-the-go. The MG20 Wireless Gaming Headphones also feature a cushioned, breathable Alcantara® headband with memory foam ear pads wrapped in lambskin for unrivaled comfort during extended gameplay, 22 hours of battery life on a single charge, and on-head detection to save battery while not in use. A low-latency USB-A adapter allows for seamless compatibility with Playstation and PC’s alike, allowing gamers to effortlessly switch between devices without having to re-pair, while Bluetooth 5.0 creates a secure connection for a 100ft/30m distance.</p>
<p><iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zyQfgIaBKLI" width="750" height="422" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
